goldwell.asia 2014-11-12

# Goldwell Company

|   
---  
  | 

Privacy Policy Title

At **Goldwell Consultants Limited** we recognize that privacy is important.   
If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us at Privacy Matters, #604, Tower A, New Trade Plaza, 6 On Ping Street, Shatin, N.T., Hong Kong 

  * **INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT**   
We offer a number of services that do not require you to register for our services or provide any personal information to us, such as Goldwell Consultants Limited Search. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:
  *  **INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE**   
When you sign up for a Goldwell Consultants Limited service or promotion that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). For certain services, such as our advertising programs, we also request credit card or other payment account information which is processed in encrypted form via PayPal services. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other Goldwell Consultants Limited services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services.
  *  **USER COMMUNICATIONS**   
When you send email or other communication to Goldwell Consultants Limited, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.
  *  **AFFILIATED SITES**   
We offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to Goldwell Consultants Limited in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.
  *  **OTHER SITES**   
This Privacy Policy applies to web sites and services that are owned and operated by Goldwell Consultants Limited. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.   
Goldwell Consultants Limited only processes personal information for the purposes described in the applicable Privacy Policy and/or privacy notice for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include:
    * Providing our products and services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising;
    * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services;
    * Ensuring the technical functioning of our network;
    * Developing new services.
  
Goldwell Consultants Limited processes personal information on our servers in the Hong Kong and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. We may process personal information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners.
  *  **CHOICES FOR PERSONAL INFORMATION**   
When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.   
If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent.   
You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case Goldwell Consultants Limited may not be able to provide those services to you.
  *  **INFORMATION SHARING**   
Goldwell Consultants Limited only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Goldwell Consultants Limited in the following limited circumstances:
    * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.
    * We provide such information to our trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
    * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable terms of service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Goldwell Consultants Limited, its users or the public as required or permitted by HK law.
  
If Goldwell Consultants Limited involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.   
We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually.   
Please contact us at the address below for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data.
  *  **INFORMATION SECURITY**   
We restrict access to personal information to Goldwell Consultants Limited employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.
  *  **DATA INTEGRITY**   
Goldwell Consultants Limited processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.
  *  **ENFORCEMENT**   
oldwell Consultants Limited regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or Goldwell Consultants Limited treatment of personal information by contacting us through this web site or by writing to us at Privacy Matters, #604, Tower A, New Trade Plaza, 6 On Ping Street, Shatin, N.T., Hong Kong   
When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is Goldwell Consultants Limited policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Goldwell Consultants Limited and an individual.
  *  **CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of the information we collect and how we use it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.   
If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this web site or at the addresses indicated previously.

© GOLDWELL CONSULTANTS LIMITED 1998-2014. All rights reserved.
